<?xml version='1.0' standalone='yes'?>	
	<epicItem>
	<title>Epsilon</title>
	<url>http://www.eclipse.org/gmt/epsilon</url>
	<category>Modeling</category>
	<description><![CDATA[Epsilon is a family of integrated model management languages for tasks such as model navigation and modification, transformation, validation, comparison, merging etc. Epsilon can be used to manage models of different modeling technologies (EMF, MDR) and is supported by Eclipse plugins (editors, outline viewers, launch configurations etc).

Epsilon also provides Eclipse-based tools for code profiling and monitoring, an ANT-based workflow for defining complex chains of model management operations, an extension of the built-in reflective EMF editor (Exeed) that enables users to customize its appearence (icons and labels) using EAnnotations attached to EClasses and EAttributes, a multi-tab editor (ModeLink) that enables users to establish arbitrary links between different EMF models (of potentially different ECore metamodels), support for defining and executing wizards - using a dedicated language (EWL) - for automating tasks (e.g. refactoring) in EMF/GMF editors, live validation in GMF-based editors, and a tool (EuGENia) that significantly speeds up the process of implementing a GMF-based editor.]]></description>
	<dateCreated>2007-02-19 09:17:17</dateCreated>
	<dateUpdated>2009-08-25 09:34:07</dateUpdated>
	<rating>9.5263</rating>
	<votes>19</votes>
	<version>0.8.7</version>
	<eclipseVersion>3.3, 3.4, 3.5</eclipseVersion>
	<licenseType>Free EPL</licenseType>
	<companyName>Eclipse.org</companyName>
	<status>Production/Stable</status>
	<buyURL><![CDATA[]]></buyURL>
	<supportURL><![CDATA[http://www.eclipse.org/gmt/epsilon/newsgroup]]></supportURL>
	<epicForum><![CDATA[]]></epicForum>
	<updateURL><![CDATA[http://download.eclipse.org/technology/gmt/epsilon/updates/]]></updateURL>
	<memberCompany>0</memberCompany>
	<imageURL>http://www-users.cs.york.ac.uk/~dkolovos/images/epsilon110x80.gif</imageURL>
	</epicItem>
	