<?xml version="1.0"?>
<examples>
	<example title="Creating an OO model with EOL" src="org.eclipse.epsilon.examples.buildooinstance">
		<language name="EOL"/>
		<description>
		This EOL program builds a simple Object Oriented model from scratch. It is 
		a useful example of the basic features of EOL.
		</description>
		<file src="/BuildOOInstance.eol"/>
	</example>
	<example title="Generating HTML for Ecore with EGL" src="org.eclipse.epsilon.examples.egldoc">
		<language name="EGL"/>
		<description>
		This application uses EGL to generate HTML-based documentation for Ecore metamodels.
		</description>
		<file src="/src/org/epsilon/egl/doc/egl/Emf2Html.egl"/>
		<file src="/src/org/epsilon/egl/doc/egl/html/Class.egl"/>
	</example>
	<example title="Running Epsilon from Java" src="org.eclipse.epsilon.examples.standalone">
		<language name="EOL"/>
		<description>
		This example shows how Epsilon can be run from Java code (without the Eclipse-based tools).
		</description>
	</example>
	<example title="Customizing Tree Editor Icons and Labels" src="org.eclipse.epsilon.examples.exeedoo">
		<language name="Exeed"/>
		<description>
		In this example, an Object Oriented ECore metamodel is annotated with Exeed-specific
		annotations so that instances of it can be visualized properly with the Exeed tree-based editor.
		(Updated 28 Feb 2007)
		</description>
	</example>
	<example title="Merging two Object Oriented models" src="org.eclipse.epsilon.examples.mergeoo">
		<language name="EML"/>
		<description>
		In this example, an ECL comparison is used to compare two Object Oriented models.
		Then its match-trace is input into an EML merging that merges the two models.
		</description>
		<file src="/MatchOO.ecl"/>
		<file src="/MergeOO.eml"/>
	</example>
	<example title="Merging an Entity model with a Vocabulary model" src="org.eclipse.epsilon.examples.mergeentitywithvocabulary">
		<language name="EML"/>
		<description>
		In this example, an ECL comparison is used to compare an Entity with a Vocabulary model.
		Then its match-trace is input into an EML merging that merges the two models. Coordination
		is achieved using the Epsilon ANT tasks. This example demonstrates that ECL and EML can be used 
		to compare/merge heterogeneous models.
		</description>
	</example>
	<example title="Validating an Object Oriented model" src="org.eclipse.epsilon.examples.validateoo">
		<language name="EVL"/>
		<description>
		This EVL validation contains constraints and  critiques that validate an Object Oriented model.
		</description>
	</example>
	<example title="Implementing Dijkstra's shortest path algorithm" src="org.eclipse.epsilon.examples.shortestpath">
		<language name="EOL"/>
		<language name="EVL"/>
		<description>
		In this project an EOL program implements Dijkstra's shortest path algorithm for
		directed graphs. Moreover,
		an EVL module validates that a graph is acyclic and has only positive weight-edges
		as required by the algorithm.
		</description>
	</example>
	<example title="Transforming an OO model into a DB model" src="org.eclipse.epsilon.examples.oo2db">
		<language name="ETL"/>
		<description>
		This ETL transformation transforms an Object Oriented model into a Relational Database model.
		The type mappings between the OO and the DB metamodel are provided in a separate Type Mapping
		model.
		</description>
	</example>
</examples>