<?xml version="1.0"?>
<users>
	<project name="NASA CertWare">
		<description>The CertWare workbench contributes several core modules supporting safety case models, and extends these with a service-based APIs for plugging new capabilities into the workbench for processing these models.</description>
		<url>http://nasa.github.com/CertWare/</url>
	</project>
	<project name="SAFECAP">
		<description>Safecap is an Eclipse-based tool for entering and analysing railway junction schemas. The tool can be used for the analysis of control table for junction signals, assessment of capacity impact of signal positioning and train detection circuit boundaries, and also for conducting semi-automatic or automatic changes to schema topology or control tables.</description>
		<url>http://safecap.sourceforge.net/</url>
	</project>
	<project name="EMF Rest">
		<description>EMF-REST generates truly RESTful APIs for your EMF models. EMF-REST complements the existing (Java-based) API generation facilities EMF already provides and extends them to the Web.</description>
		<url>http://emf-rest.com/</url>
	</project>
	<project name="MTC Flow">
		<description>MTC Flow s a tool which allows model-driven developers to design, develop, test and deploy Model Transformation Chains (MTCs). The tool offers a graphical DSL for defining MTC workflows independently of implementation technologies.</description>
		<url>http://mtcflow.com/</url>
	</project>
	<project name="Melanee">
		<description>Melanee is a workbench for creating domain-specific languages which occupy an arbitrary number of ontological levels. It ships with a default general-purpose notation which is designed with the UML and Entity-Relationship diagrams in mind.</description>
		<url>http://melanee.org/</url>
	</project>
	<project name="JastEMF">
		<description>JastEMF is a tool to support the integrated use of the JastAdd system - a rewriteable, circular, reference attribute grammar (ReCRAG) generator - and the Eclipse Modeling Framework (EMF) - a Java based metamodeling framework built around the Ecore metamodeling language.</description>
		<url>https://code.google.com/a/eclipselabs.org/p/jastemf/</url>
		<evidence>https://code.google.com/a/eclipselabs.org/p/jastemf/source/browse/trunk/jastemf-examples/statemachine/specifications/metamodel/Statemachine.ecore?spec=svn388&amp;r=388&amp;redir=1</evidence>
	</project>	
	<project name="HiLeS">
		<description>The HiLeS2 Framework was developed to aid the Embedded System Designers during the design process. The HiLeS2 Framework purpose is to serve as a platform to create Embedded System Product Lines. It incorporates both tools developed by the group and open source tools to provide an Integrated Development Environment (IDE) suitable for system specification, product line construction and virtual prototype generation.</description>
		<url>https://hiles.uniandes.edu.co/</url>
	</project>
	<project name="Mosskit">
		<description>Modeling Software KIT (MOSKitt) is a FREE CASE tool, built on Eclipse which is being developed by the Conselleria de Infraestructuras, Territorio y Medio Ambiente to support the gvMétrica methodology (adapting Métrica III to its specific needs). gvMétrica uses techniques based on the UML modeling language. MOSKitt's plugin architecture makes it not only a CASE Tool but also a Free Modeling Platform to develop this kind of tools.</description>
		<url>http://www.moskitt.org/eng/</url>
	</project>
	<project name="metaDepth">
		<description>metaDepth is a framework for deep meta-modelling that provide supports for an arbitrary number of ontological meta-levels. This makes MetaDepth especially useful to define multi-level languages.</description>
		<url>http://astreo.ii.uam.es/~jlara/metaDepth/</url>
	</project>
	<project name="bflow* Toolbox">
		<description>The bflow* Toolbox is an open source tool kit for business process management. The objective of bflow* is to explore new ways and scenarios for the development and use of modelling tools.
		</description>
		<url>http://sourceforge.net/projects/bflowtoolbox/</url>
		<evidence>https://svn.code.sf.net/p/bflowtoolbox/code/trunk/plugins/org.bflow.toolbox.oepc.evl/validation/syntax.evl</evidence>
	</project>	
	<project name="Pongo MongoDB Generator">
		<description>Pongo is a template-based Java POJO generator for MongoDB. Instead of using low-level DBObjects to interact with your MongoDB database, with Pongo you can define your data/domain model using Emfatic and then generate strongly-typed Java classes you can then use to work with your database at a more convenient level of abstraction.</description>
		<url>https://code.google.com/p/pongo/</url>
	</project>	
	<project name="TENTE C#">
		<description>TENTE is a contribution for SPL architectural design and implementation. This process integrates relevant advances, from an SPL point of view, for separation of concerns and MDD technologies. This project contains the TENTE code generators for the C# approach.</description>
		<url>https://code.google.com/p/tentecsharp/</url>
	</project>
	<project name="Brics">
		<description>The prime objective of BRICS is to structure and formalize the robot development process itself and to provide tools, models, and functional libraries, which help accelerating this process significantly.</description>
		<url>http://www.best-of-robotics.org/</url>
	</project>
	<project name="MIDE">
		<description>MIDE is an IDE for working with UML Class Diagrams. It extends the Eclipse UML2 Editor and enables carrying out complex tasks in one click, and provides a pattern-matching engine for detecting design errors as soon as they are made</description>
		<url>http://sourceforge.net/projects/mide-bgu/</url>
	</project>
	<project name="Event-B">
		<url>http://wiki.event-b.org/index.php/Transformation_patterns</url>
		<description>Event-B is a formal method for system-level modelling and analysis. Key features of Event-B are the use of set theory as a modelling notation, the use of refinement to represent systems at different abstraction levels and the use of mathematical proof to verify consistency between refinement levels.</description>
	</project>	
	<project name="PhpNoDB">
		<description>While having a database is essential for any large-scale website, it can be an overkill for smaller projects/prototypes where read-only access to a small dataset would be sufficient. To save you the trouble of setting up and managing a database if you don't really need one, phpnodb lets you capture your data in a Google Spreadsheet and then generate from it a standalone PHP class that contains an embedded copy of your data.</description>
		<url>https://code.google.com/p/phpnodb/</url>
	</project>
	<project name="Collaborative Modeling Framework">
		<description>This modeling framework uses the MetaDepth framework to model and generate collaborative Android applications. The framework includes - among others - chat, Dropbox, Foursquare and geo components. </description>
		<url>https://github.com/philipdesmedt/Thesis-Android</url>
	</project>
	<project name="Product Line Documentation Toolkit for Eclipse">
		<description>The aim of the project is to create an Eclipse plugin to support text and visual editing and validating of DRL documents. DRL stands for 'Document Reuse Language' - a special document markup language incorporating docbook features, designed for creating documentation for a series of highly-interrelated software products, otherwise known as 'Product Line'.
		</description>
		<url>https://code.google.com/p/pldoctoolkit/</url>
		<evidence>https://code.google.com/p/pldoctoolkit/source/browse/trunk/plwebmldoc/org.eclipse.gmf.webml/model/webml.emf</evidence>
	</project>
	<project name="Context Manager Framework">
		<description>Context Manager Framework is a ongoing work at Department of Engineering and Computer Science and Mathematics at University of L'Aquila. It includes model-based methodologies and tools to support the non-functional (a.k.a. extra-functional)aspects of context-aware software systems.
		</description>
		<url>https://code.google.com/a/eclipselabs.org/p/context-manager/</url>
		<evidence>https://code.google.com/a/eclipselabs.org/p/context-manager/source/browse/mngr/model/exp.emf</evidence>
	</project>
	<project name="Design Framework for Embedded Systems">
		<description>The Design Framework is a tool that helps you to link all design activities to concrete design artifacts and to track consistency of these artefacts</description>
		<url>http://df.esi.nl/</url>
	</project>
	<project name="UNC Chapel Hill Libraries">
		<description>University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill Libraries open-source project. Library metadata models and mapping tools implemented in Eclipse Modelling Framework (EMF).</description>
		<url>https://github.com/UNC-Libraries/</url>
	</project>
	<project name="MetaGem">
		<description>MeTAGeM is a Meta-Tool for the Automatic Generation of Model Transformations that makes possible to put into practice the MDE (Model-Driven Engineering) principles for developing model transformations, defining model transformations as models, without considering details of the code implementation.</description>
		<url>http://metagem.wordpress.com/</url>
		<evidence>http://metagem.googlecode.com/svn-history/r461/trunk/MeTAGeM.ui/src/kybele/metagem/ui/api/resources/mm_Hybrid_to_RubyTL.evl</evidence>
	</project>
	<project name="Unicaneer2Sql">
		<url>http://code.google.com/p/unicaneer2sql/</url>
		<description>An Eclipse plugin for model-driven development of databases. The application provides facilities to create graphical ER models and generates code for SLQ Sever and Oracle.</description>
	</project>
	<project name="Reflo">
		<url>http://code.google.com/a/eclipselabs.org/p/reflo/</url>
		<description>This project aims to provide a machine-assisted environment for developers model programs, using a dataflow notation. It also provides a rewriting system for dataflow graphs.</description>
	</project>	
	<project name="Kybele GMF Gen">
		<url>http://kybelegmfgen.googlecode.com</url>
		<description>Kybele GMF Generator (also known as KybeleGMFgen) is a new Model-Driven Software Development (MDSD) tool for Eclipse Modeling Tools for creating, in only a few steps, graphical editors from manually annotated metamodels and customization files.</description>
	</project>
	<!--project name="GenGMF">
		<description>GMF model generator</description>
		<url>http://gengmf.randomice.net/</url>
	</project-->	
</users>