<?xml version="1.0"?>
<articles>
	<article name="emfatic" title="Emfatic language reference" content="html">
		<description>
		This article provides a complete reference of the syntax of Emfatic, which is a textual language for specifying Ecore metamodels.
		</description>
	</article>
	<article name="extended-properties" title="Extended Properties">
		<description>
		This article demonstrates the extended properties mechanism in EOL (and by inheritance, in all languages in Epsilon).
		</description>
	</article>
	<article name="call-java-from-epsilon" title="Call Java from Epsilon">
		<description>
		This article demonstrates how to create Java objects, access their properties and call their methods from Epsilon languages.
		</description>
	</article>
<article name="eol-syntax-updates" title="EOL syntax updates">
		<description>
		This article summarizes the changes introduced in 0.8.7 and 0.8.8 in the EOL concrete syntax. 
		</description>
	</article>
	<article name="egl-server-side" title="EGL as a server-side language">
		<description>
		This article demonstrates using EGL (the model-to-text language of Epsilon) in Tomcat to produce HTML pages from EMF models on the fly.
		</description>
	</article>
	<article name="eugenia-gmf-tutorial" title="EuGENia GMF Tutorial">
		<description>
		This article provides a guide to using EuGENia for developing GMF editors, as well as its complete list of features and supported annotations.
		</description>
	</article>
	<article name="eugenia-polishing" title="Customizing an editor generated with EuGENia">
		<description>
		This article demonstrates how a GMF editor generated with EuGENia can be polished in a systematic and reproducible way.
		</description>
	</article>
	<article name="evl-gmf-integration" title="EVL-GMF Integration">
		<description>
		This article demonstrates evaluating EVL constraints from within a GMF-based editor.
		</description>
	</article>
	<article name="eugenia-nodes-with-images" title="EuGENia: Nodes with images instead of shapes">
		<description>
		This article shows how to create nodes in your GMF editor that are represented with images (png, jpg etc.) instead of the standard GMF shapes (rectangle, ellipse etc.)
		</description>
	</article>
	<article name="eugenia-nodes-with-runtime-images" title="EuGENia: Nodes with images defined at run-time">
		<description>
		This article addresses the case where the end-user needs to set an image for each node at runtime.
		</description>
	</article>	
	<article name="eugenia-phantom-nodes" title="EuGENia: Phantom nodes in GMF editors">
		<description>
		This article demonstrates how to define GMF phantom nodes in EuGENia.
		</description>
	</article>
	<article name="epackage-registry-view" title="The EMF EPackage Registry View">
		<description>
		This article demonstrates the EPackage Registry view which allows developers to inspect the contents of the registered EMF EPackages.
		</description>
	</article>
	<article name="epsilon-source-svn" title="Getting the source code of Epsilon">
		<description>
		This article demonstrates how to obtain and run a local copy of the source code of Epsilon.
		</description>
	</article>
	<article name="manage-the-epsilon-website-locally" title="Manage the Epsilon website locally">
		<description>
		This article demonstrates how to manage the Epsilon website in your machine.
		</description>
	</article>
</articles>